(Penny:)Why don't I pour it in your lap
and you can tell me?
(Sheldon:)You don't have to be mean. I'm sick.
(Penny:)-Yeah, well, I'm sick too.
-Not my problem.
I don't understand
how this happened to me.
(Sheldon:)I'm scrupulous about my hygiene,
I regularly disinfect my hands...
(Sheldon:)...and I avoid contact with other people
on general principle.
(Penny:)I don't know what to tell you,
Sheldon.
SHELDON:
Oh, Penny, thank you.
(Penny:)You're welcome.
It's you. I touched you.
(Penny:)Happy Valentine's Day.
(Raj:)Oh, my goodness, look at this room.
[GASPS]
Champagne, roses,
oh, and little chocolates.
(Raj:)This is going to be
the best Valentine's Day ever.
(Leonard:)Yeah, I forgot about all this.
(Raj:)But I never will.